{
    "subject": "resource/Var\u0101hamihira",
    "predicate": "ontology/notableWork",
    "object": "resource/Var\u0101hamihira",
    "human_readable": "Var\u0101hamihira's notable work is Var\u0101hamihira.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9730581641197205,
            "question": "Can you name a famous work by Var\u0101hamihira?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9650765061378479,
            "question": "Were there any other notable works by Var\u0101hamihira besides 'Var\u0101hamihira'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9522150754928589,
            "question": "What type of work is 'Var\u0101hamihira'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9184916615486145,
            "question": "What is Var\u0101hamihira known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9105603098869324,
            "question": "Who wrote the work 'Var\u0101hamihira'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8473708033561707,
            "question": "Where did Var\u0101hamihira live and work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7373313903808594,
            "question": "What field of study is Var\u0101hamihira associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7208104729652405,
            "question": "Is Var\u0101hamihira considered an important figure in history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6741681694984436,
            "question": "What are some key themes explored in 'Var\u0101hamihira'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6312751173973083,
            "question": "What time period was Var\u0101hamihira active in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Var\u0101hamihira's notable work is Var\u0101hamihira.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8396_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some key themes explored in 'Var\u0101hamihira'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8396_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Var\u0101hamihira considered an important figure in history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8396_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field of study is Var\u0101hamihira associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8396_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8396_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8396_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8396_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8396_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8396_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8396_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8396_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8396_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8396_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8396_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries!  I'm ready for more. \ud83d\ude0a \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents contain information about Var\u0101hamihira, including his notable works, such as Brihat Samhita and Pancha Siddhantika. However, they do not mention Var\u0101hamihira's notable work being simply \"Var\u0101hamihira\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The triple \"Var\u0101hamihira's notable work is Var\u0101hamihira\" is incorrect. According to the context information provided, Var\u0101hamihira's notable works include \"Pancha Siddhantika\" and \"Brihat Samhita\". Therefore, the statement that his notable work is simply named after him is not supported by the given documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}